http://www.landauinc.com/our-work/environmental-site-management-and-engineering/privacy-policy

Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy This Privacy Statement describes the types of personal information Landau Associates, Inc. collects through the website located at www.landauinc.com (the “Site”), and how we use, share and protect that information. This Privacy Statement does not govern the collection of information through any website, or any other means, other than through the Site.
Personal Information We Collect and How We Use ItWe do not collect personal information through the Site unless you voluntarily provide such information to us. Personal information such as name and email address is collected through the Site from visitors who submit a request for information by sending e-mail through the Site. We use personal information to respond to your inquiries or for any other purposes for which you provide such information.Tracking and CookiesOur web server automatically recognizes and records certain information about visitors to the Site. This includes date and time of access, IP address, web browser type and version, and address of the website from which you entered the Site. The web server does not record email addresses. We use this information only to optimize and improve the content of the Site.We use temporary, session-specific cookies to track website traffic. Cookies do not reveal or contain any identifying or personal data, cannot read any information on your computer, and cannot interact with other cookies on your hard drive. Cookies stay on the user’s hard drive to identify site visits and whether the user is a returning visitor.Information We ShareWe do not sell, rent, or otherwise share personal information about visitors of the Site, except as described herein. We may share non-personal information with third parties who provide us statistical information about the use of the Site.Information SecurityWe undertake reasonable security measures to protect the information collected through the Site. While we place a priority on the security of personally identifiable information, we cannot guarantee the security of any information you transmit to us through the Site.Links to Other WebsitesThe Site may contain links to external websites for your convenience. We do not endorse these websites and are not responsible for the content, accuracy, or privacy practices of such websites.Updates to this Privacy StatementWe may change this Privacy Statement at any time without prior notice to you. We will post a notice on the home page of the Site to notify you of any significant changes to this Privacy Statement.How to Contact UsIf you have any questions or comments about this Privacy Statement, please email us at info@landauinc.com.
Contact Us Tell us more about
your
project.
Contact Us
Edmonds130 2nd Avenue SouthEdmonds, WA 98020Phone (425) 778-0907Email UsGet Directions
500 Columbia St NW, Ste 110Olympia, WA 98501Phone (360) 791-3178Email UsGet Directions
QuincyPO Box 37Quincy, WA 98848Phone  (253) 926-2493Email UsGet Directions
Spokane10 North Post Street, Ste 218Spokane, WA 99201Phone (509) 327-9737Email UsGet Directions
Portland
1500 SW 1st Avenue, Ste 1015Portland, OR 97201Phone (503) 542-1080Email UsGet Directions
Copyright © 2019 Landau Associates | All rights reserved | Privacy Statement
| Website designed by Olive Street Design
Share by:
